Guide to the National Grange of the Patrons of Husbandry records, 1842-1994
National Grange of the Patrons of Husbandry records, 1842-1994
- Series I. National Master - William Saunders 1867-1873
  - Garvin, W. L. History of the Grant State Farmer's Alliance of Texas. (pamphlet) Jackson, Texas: A. Zeese & Co., 1885 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - U.S. Department of Agriculture. Report of the Secretary of Agriculture. Washington: Government Printing Office., 1894 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Dorsett, P.H., A.D. Shamel, and Wilson Popenoe. The Navel Orange of Bahia. U.S. Department of Agriculture Bulletin No. 445. Washington: Government Printing Office., 1917 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Periodical and Newspaper Clippings (obituaries and tributes), 1900-1929 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Draft of Catalog of Economic Plants in the collection of the U.S. Department of Agriculture, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Oversize plans - International Exhibition, 1876 (Map-case Folder 1)
- Series II. National Secretary - Oliver H. Kelley 1867-1878
  - Professional Business Papers, 1865-1913 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    Includes Isaac Newton, William Saunders, Oliver H. Kelley, U.S. Department of Agriculture, National Grange.
  - Family Papers, 1842-1926 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    Family death register, engraved booklet with handwritten notes, telegram, newspaper clipping, manuscript correspondence, memorabilia.
  - Caroline A. Hall items, 1868, 1869 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    Includes Francis M. McDowell, Oliver H. Kelley, National Grange.
- Series III. National Grange: State Granges and Oklahoma Grange
  - "Ballot list of Officers elected at the sixth annual session, and the second election of Officers in the National Grange, Friday, January 10, 1873, 5 o'clock p.m." (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - National Grange of the Patrons of Husbandry. Seventh Annual Session. Declaration of Purposes of the National Grange, with handwritten notes., 1874 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Multicopies of correspondence, reports, articles, engraving., 1868-1887 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Includes Oliver H. Kelley, W. W. Corbett, National Grange, Bryan Publications.
  - National Grange Scrapbook, 1897-1954 (Box 9, Folder 4 (a-e))
    Correspondence, biographical information; newspaper articles, photographs, pamphlets. Includes William M. King, W. H. Landvoight, Louis J. Taber, Belle Saunders.
  - Correspondence, certificates, 1911-1959 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Includes Mortimer Whitehead, Harold Cornell, Herschel Newsom, Franklin Delano Roosevelt, Executive Committee.
  - Classified Price List of Books Suited to the Wants of Grange Libraries. New York: Grange Publishing Co., c. 1875 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - National Grange. Handbuch der Untergeordneten Granges der Patrone der Landwirthlschaft. Philadelphia: T. U. Wagenjeller., 1877 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Record Book of Westfield Grange No. 809 P. of H. [Ill.] (v.b.), 1873-1882 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    Includes J. M. Mitchell, Mrs. Mitchell, Westfield Grange, Illinois.
  - Massachusetts State Grange, 1875 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - New York State Grange. Proceedings of the Fourth Annual Session. Elmira, N.Y.: Husbandman Press, Farmers' Club-Hall., 1877 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Virginia State Grange. Journal of Proceedings of the Twelfth Annual Session. Winchester, Virginia: Patrons of Husbandry., 1939 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Virginia State Grange Data, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    Correspondence, notes, pamphlet, resolutions, news clippings. Includes Charles H. Gardner, National Grange.
  - Executive Committee (v.b.), 1928 (Box 9)
    Constitution, by-laws, rules and regulations. Includes Albert S. Goss.
  - National Grange Record Book (v.b.), 1867 (Box 9)
    Signed pledge, illuminated title page.
  - National Grange. Manual and Monitor of Subordinate Granges. Pioneer Printing Company, St. Paul, Minn. (Letter attached. Original letter in Box 1 Folder 2)), 1869 (Box 9)
  - National Grange. Manual of Subordinate Granges of the Patrons of Husbandry. Fifth Edition, 1874 (Box 9)
  - Ohio State Grange. Hints and Helps to Profit and Pleasure in the Grange. Springfield, Ohio: Live Patron Office., 1881 (Box 9)
  - National Grange ledger (v.b.), 1873-1907 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - National Grange ledger (v.b.), 1880, 1909-1919 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - National Grange journal (v.b.), 1907-1926 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - National Grange records, minutes (v.b.), 1920-1938 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Oklahoma State Grange letters, minutes (v.b.), 1916-1919 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Oklahoma State Grange minutes (v.b.), 1916, 1919-1929 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Series IV. National Master - Albert S. Goss, 1941-1950
  - "Acts of Incorporation, Constitution, and By-Laws", 1948, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    Copies of Act, Constitution, By-laws, articles, correspondence, application. Includes Ambrose G. Measure, Winton Wedemeyer, Montana State Grange.
  - "Agricultural Economics - Sources of Information" (pamphlet), 1943 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - "Bonding", 1948 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    Correspondence and application for bond coverage.
  - "Carrick, Richard C.", 1943-1945 (Box 11, Folder 4, 5)
    Correspondence, note, news clippings, list, by-laws, schedule, editorial. Includes National Grange Mutual Liability Co.
  - "Degree", 1926 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    Manual, reasons.
  - "Deputy Material", 1949, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    Resolutions, news clipping, notes, correspondence, Master's Address material.
  - "Digest" [Sources of Master's Address] - news clippings, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - "Effects of Graduated Income Tax Rates on Farm Investments" - correspondence, 1944 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - "Estate and Gift Taxes", 1942-1950 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    Note, pamphlets, forms.
  - "Extension Rules", 1933-1951 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - "Farm Credit", Jan. 9, 1943 - Aug. 1, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 12-15)
    Reports, statements, memos, minutes, notes, pamphlets, correspondence, speech, bill resolution, news clipping. Includes R. W. Mize, I. W. Duggan, Raymond S. Fouts, J. R. Isleib, Thomas H. Roberts, Farm Credit Administration (U.S. Department of Agriculture), National Farm Loan Association.
  - Farm Credit Act of 1952, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    Draft, summary, amendment.
  - Farm Credit Administration: Economic and Credit Research Division, 1943 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    Reports, charts.
  - FCA Miscellaneous, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 18, 19)
    Correspondence, reports, analysis, comments. Includes A. G. Black, National Council of Farmer Cooperatives, Farm Credit Administration.
  - "Current F.C.A. Reports in Making", 1941 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    Correspondence, drafts, address, list. Includes Robert McConnaughey, United States Department of Agriculture.
  - Farm Credit Association - Contents of Envelope, 1938-1941 (Box 11, Folder 21, 22)
    List of contents, notes, correspondence, suggestions, remarks, tables, memos, statements, releases, report.
  - Farm Credit Legislation, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 23-25)
    Correspondence, notes, memo, proposals, draft Bill, progress reports. Includes Louis J. Taber, National Grange.
  - "Farm Foundation" (pamphlet), 1943 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Farm Mortgage Bankers Bill, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    Notes, plan, correspondence, clipping. Includes H. G. Green, Commerce Mortgage Company.
  - Farmers and Traders Life Insurance Co., 1942, 1944 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    Includes Louis J. Taber, Martin W. Lammers.
  - Farmers Automobile Inter-Insurance Exchange, 1942-1945 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    Minutes, tables, pamphlet.
  - Albert S. Goss news clippings, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Grange Cooperative Wholesale 1949-1951, 1949, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    Correspondence, summary, reports, pamphlets, note, statement. Includes W. J. Wilcox, Elmer McClure, Paul Taber, W. T. Smith, Oregon State Grange.
  - Grange Correspondence - Miscellaneous, 1947, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Income Parity, 1942, 1943 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    Resolution, paper, charts, correspondence.
  - Inflation and Miscellaneous, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    Correspondence, address, charts, tear sheet, Bill, memo, notes, news clippings. Includes Harry B. Caldwell, North Carolina State Grange.
  - "International Institute of Agriculture", 1930, 1933, 1945 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    Correspondence, narrative, articles, pamphlets. Includes Henry C. Taylor, Farm Foundation.
  - Master's Address, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    Draft, news clipping
  - Master's Address - Notes, 1941, 1943, 1944 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Master's Addresses - Drafts and Notes, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Master's Address - Notes, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Master's Address - Drafts, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 40, 41)
    Drafts, addresses, memos, recommendations, testimony, news clipings, pamphlets, notes.
  - Master's Address - Copy, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Miscellaneous, c. 1939, 1941, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - National Grange. Digest 1928. Constitution and Digest of the Laws and Enactments of the Order of Patrons of Husbandry. (Box 11, Folder missing)
  - National Grange Monthly, 1944, 1947, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 43)
    Correspondence, questionnaire, reports, notes. Includes William A. Ayres, Gilbert T. Richardson.
  - National Grange Mutual Liability Company and Fire Insurance Company, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 44)
    News clippings, reports.
  - National Grange Stabilization Proposal, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 45)
    Proposal, news releases.
  - Parity Prices, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 46)
    Tables, news clippings.
  - "Personnel", 1945, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 47)
    Correspondence, data, photos, pamphlets. Includes John D. Hervey.
  - The President's Labor Day Message, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Price Control, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 49)
    Tables, reports.
  - Radio Addresses, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Rulings, 1936-1950 (Box 11, Folder 51, 52)
    Correspondence, by-laws. Includes Morton Tompkins, Charles Clifford, Oregon State Grange, Farmington Grange #49. (Connecticut)
  - State Granges, 1942, 1946, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 53)
    Pamphlet, excerpt from book, correspondence. Includes Mississippi, Texas, South Dakota, Tennessee State Granges.
  - Statements on Inflation, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Statements on Parity, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - State Situations [Pennsylvania], 1950 (Box 11, Folder 56)
    Correspondence, notice of appeal. Includes W. Sharp Fullerton, H. M. Burchinal, Pennsylvania State Grange.
  - State Situations [Washington], 1950 (Box 11, Folder 57)
    Correspondence, statement, notice, resolution, memo, report. Includes Elizabeth Carstensen, Edgar J. Wright, Washington State Grange.
  - Subjects for Articles, 1934, 1938, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 58)
    Articles, notes, memos, correspondence, report, tear sheet.
  - Subordinate Grange Tax - correspondence, 1944 (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - Taber Correspondence, 1928-1943 (Box 11, Folder 60)
    Correspondence, news clipping, resolution. Includes Louis J. Taber, R. M. Whittaker, National Grange Feeds, Inc.
  - Taber - Executive Committee, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 61)
    Correspondence, statement. Includes Louis J. Taber, National Grange.
  - Tobacco, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 62)
    Suggested program, tables, pamphlet - Tobacco Committee of the National Grange.
- Series V. Herschel D. Newsom
  - Agriculture Commodity Stabilization Service, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    Includes James McConnell, U.S. Department of Agriculture - Commodity Stabilization Service.
  - American Farm Bureau Federation, 1948, 1954-1956 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    Correspondence, reports, news clippings, pamphlets. Includes Charles B. Shuman.
  - American Institute of Cooperation, 1954-1956 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    Correspondence, paper, pamphlets - farm cooperatives. Includes J. K. Stern, American Institute of Cooperation.
  - Annual Session, Colorado, 1955, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 4 (a-f))
    Memos, programs, brochures. Includes Stuart Symington, United States Senate.
  - "B", 1952, 1954-1958 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    Correspondence, interview, handbook, report (multi-copy); carbon address, death notices. Includes Earl L. Butz, T. W. Braun, Purdue University, Braun and Company.
  - "E. Carroll Bean", 1948, 1952-1956 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    Correspondence, memos, newsletter, lists, news clippings - grange ritual. Includes Harry A. Caton, National Grange (High Priest of Demeter.)
  - Bennett, Charles Dana, 1955-1957 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    Correspondence, memo, talk, budgets. Includes Foundation for American Agriculture.
  - Bonding Program, 1947-1955 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    Correspondence, circular, memos, bond, policy. Includes Albert S. Goss, C. B. Fowler, National Grange, National Grange Mutual Liability Co.
  - Bonding Correspondence, 1947 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Cash Contributions - Building Fund, 1948-1955 (Box 12, Folder 10 (a, b))
    Correspondence, reports, memo. Includes National Grange Building Fund, Eunice Hoffman.
  - Building - National Grange, 1943-1951, 1943-1953 (Box 12, Folder 11 (a-f))
    Correspondence, notes, reports, statements, release, invoices. Includes Richard C. Carrick, Thomas B. Lawler, W. G. Armstrong, Eunice Hoffman, Albert S. Goss, National Grange Mutual Liability Co., International Bank of Washington, D.C., Michigan State Grange.
  - Building, 1953, 1955, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    Correspondence, financial statements, news clipping. Includes John W. Cragun, Wilkinson, Cragun, Barker and Hawkins Law Offices.
  - "C", 1955-1958 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    Correspondence, informational folder. Includes Clifton B. Cox, Purdue University.
  - Caton, Harry A., 1951-1958 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    Correspondence, statistics, memo, handbooks.
  - Chairs from Home Economics Committee for Conference Room, 1948, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    List, article.
  - Congressional Letters re Building, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 16 (a, b))
    Correspondence, newsletters, news clipping, bills. Includes James G. Polk, Charles O. Porter, F. Moran McConihe, U.S. Congress (House of Representatives), General Services Administration.
  - Convention, 1956, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 17 (a-g))
    Correspondence, news clipping, ballots, photograph, progams, memos. Includes Henry Christensen, Harry Caldwell, Colorado State Grange, National Grange.
  - Convention - 1958, 1956-1958 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    Telegrams, correspondence, memos, news clippings, programs. Includes Richard Nixon, Ezra Taft Benson, Roy Battles, U.S. Department of Agriculture.
  - Deputy Compensation - Rule 3 (G), 1954 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    Correspondence, applications.
  - Deputy Master Files re Grange Extension, 1950, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 21 (a-f))
    Correspondence, memos. Includes John D. Hervey, Albert S. Goss, Herschel D. Newsom.
  - Dues and Membership Tabulations 1911-1944, 1948 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Farm Credit I, 1948, 1950 - 1954 (Box 12, Folder 23 (a-r))
    Communications, notes, correspondence, drafts, news clippings, statements, memos, telegrams, Bills, pamphlets. Includes T. Harvey Hedgepeth, Herschel D. Newsom, Lloyd C. Halvorson, Sam H. Bober, Ezra Taft Benson, Hedgepeth and Norsworth, National Farm Loan Associations, Advisory Committee.
  - Farm Credit II, 1945-1954 (Box 13, Folder 1 (a-j))
    Reports, agendas, notes, communications, drafts, statements, correspondence, news clippings, photographs, Bills, pamphlets. Includes Albert S. Goss, Sam Sober, T. Harvey Hedgepeth, E. W. McMindes, National Farm Loan Association, Advisory Committee, Hedgepeth and Norsworth, Production Credit Association.
  - Charles M. Gardner, 1952-1954 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    Correspondence, poster, newsletters, news clippings, biographical sketch, tribute, notes. Includes Charles M. Gardner, Elizabeth H. Gardner.
  - Grange History, 1949, 1951, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 3 (a, b, c))
    Correspondence, history, statement, auditor's certificates. Includes Charles W. Braseell, Charles M. Gardner.
  - Grange Membership Relations Trust Fund, 1956, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    Includes Louis J. Taber, C. M. Hall, Alvin Hanson, Farmers and Traders Life Insurance Co., National Grange Monthly.
  - Grange Song - music sheets and song books, 1936 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Insurance Information - correspondence, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - 736 Jackson Place, 1954, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    Correspondence, notes, memo, rental. Includes Delos L. James.
  - Leaders' Conferences, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    Lists, schedule, minutes, reports.
  - National Grange Monthly, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 9 (a, b, c))
    Correspondence, charts, minutes, resolution, newspapers. Includes James C. Farmer, C. M. Hall, R. C. Carrick, Alvin E. Hanson, E. T. Taylor, National Grange Mutual Liability Co., Farmers and Traders Life Insurance Co., Grange Mutual Insurance Co.
  - "N.G.M" Committee, 1954, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    Correspondence, lists, pamphlets. Includes James C. Farmer, National Grange Fire Insurance Co.
  - Statement of Expenditures and Disbursements, 1952, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Trust Fund, 1955, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 12 (#1 - a, b, c))
    Correspondence, Declaration of Trust, reports, Telefax on National Grange Monthly Publishing Co. Includes Carl S. Hawkins, C. M. Hall, R. C. Carrick, Wilkinson, Crogun, Barker and Hawkins, Law Offices (formerly Wilkinson, Boyden, Crogun and Barker), National Grange Monthly, National Grange Mutual Liability Co.
  - Trust Fund, 1956-1958 (Box 13, Folder 13 (#2 - a, b, c))
    Correspondence, reports on Grange Membership Relations and Advertising Trust Fund. Includes C. M. Hall, R. C. Carrick, C. N. Silcox, National Grange Monthly, National Grange Mutual Liability Co., Cooperative Grange League Federation Exchange Inc.
  - United Nations Expanded Technical Assistance Program, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    I - Technical Assistance Chronology
    II - Russia Wanted Centralization
    III - Key Personalities
    IV - Clippings
    V - Biographies
    VI - Background
    List, despatch, chronology, reports, chart, articles, clippings, booklets.
- Series VI. Diamond Jubilee Building Fund 1940-1942
  State correspondence, report cards, applications.
  - Arizona - application, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Arizona - lists, correspondence, 1942 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - California, Sept. 1, 1941 - Oct. 14, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - California, Oct. 14, 1941 - July 1942 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Colorado, 1941, 1942 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Connecticut, 1941, 1942 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Delaware, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - District of Columbia, 1941, 1942 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Idaho, 1941, 1942 (Box 13, Folder 23 (a, b))
  - Illinois, 1941, 1942 (Box 13, Folder 24 (a, b))
  - Indiana, 1941, 1942 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Iowa, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Kansas, 1940-1942 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Maine, 1941, 1942 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Maryland, 1941, 1942 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Massachusetts, 1941, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 1 (a, b))
  - Michigan, 1941, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 2 (a, b, c))
  - Minnesota, 1940-1942 (Box 14, Folder 3 (a, b))
  - Missouri, 1941 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Montana, 1941, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Nebraska, 1941 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Nevada, 1941, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - New Hampshire, 1941, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - New Jersey, 1941, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 9 (a, b))
  - New York, Dec. 1940 - Oct. 16, 1941 (Box 14, Folder 10(a-d))
  - New York, Oct. 16, 1941 - Dec. 8, 1941 (Box 14, Folder 11 (a, b, c))
  - New York, Dec. 8, 1941 - Aug. 31, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 12 (a, b))
  - North Carolina, 1941, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Ohio, Dec. 1940 - Sept. 1, 1941 (Box 14, Folder 14 (a-d))
  - Ohio, Sept. 1, 1941 - Oct. 15, 1941 (Box 14, Folder 15 (a-d))
  - Ohio, Oct. 15, 1941, - Dec. 8, 1941 (Box 14, Folder 16 (a, b, c))
  - Ohio, Dec. 8, 1941 - Aug. 5, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 17 (a, b))
  - Oklahoma, 1941 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Oregon, 1941, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 19 (a, b, c))
  - Pennsylvania, Dec. 1940 - Dec. 8, 1941 (Box 14, Folder 20 (a, b, c))
  - Pennsylvania, Dec. 8, 1941 - Aug. 31, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 21 (a, b))
  - Rhode Island, 1941, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - South Carolina, 1941, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - South Dakota, 1941 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Tennessee, 1941 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Texas, 1941 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Vermont, 1940-1942 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Virginia, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Washington, 1940-1942 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - West Virginia, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Wisconsin, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Wyoming, 1941, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Western Financial Founders - Patrons securing 2 or more members, 1941, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    Correspondence, lists, Founder's blanks.
- Series VII. Transportation Consultant - Charles Bowling
  - Charles B. Bowling, Personal File, 1959-1961 (Box 15, Folder 7 (a, b, c))
    Correspondence, notes, expense accounts, certificate.
  - Transportation Subject File "A", 1949, 1959-1963 (Box 15, Folder 8 (a, b))
    Correspondence, notes, talk, statement, Bill, pamphlets, periodicals, newsletter. Includes W. Ray Alexander.
  - Transportation: "B", 1959, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    Correspondence, Bill.
  - Transportation: "C", 1959, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 10 (a, b))
    Correspondence, draft, resume, appeal, recommendation, telegram, notes. Includes Harry B. Caldwell, E. E. Allison, North Carolina State Grange, Committee Against Unauthorized Transportation.
  - Transportation: "E", 1960 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    Correspondence, reports. Includes S. N. Halvorson, Equity Supply Company.
  - Transportation: "F", 1957, 1959, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    Correspondence, pamphlets, newsletter, statement, report.
  - Transportation: "G", 1959, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    Correspondence, remarks.
  - Transportation: "H", 1956, 1958, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    Correspondence, news bulletin. Includes J. W. Harnack, Cooperative Grange League Federation Exchange, Inc.
  - Transportation: "I, J, K", 1957-1962 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    Correspondence, report, newsletter.
  - Transportation: "L", 1959, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    Correspondence, address, pamphlet.
  - Transportation: "M", 1956, 1959, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    Correspondence, Bill, pamphlet.
  - Transportation: "N", 1959, 1960, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    Correspondence, remarks, newsletters, pamphlets.
  - Transportation: "O, P", 1956, 1959, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    Correspondence, pamphlet, newsletter.
  - Transportation: "R", 1959, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    Correspondence, newsletters.
  - Transportation: "S", 1959, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    Correspondence, program, memo, address.
  - Transportation: "T", 1952, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    Correspondence, memo, editorial, testimony.
  - Transportation: "U", 1953, 1959, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    Correspondence, statement, pamphlet, newsletter.
  - Transportation: "W", 1959, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    Newsletters, address, memo.
  - Agricultural Exemptions, 1953, 1960, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    Correspondence, memos, submission, statement. Includes James L. Pease, United States Department of Agriculture.
  - Agricultural Transportation Committee, 1946-1966 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    Correspondence, reports, newsletters, releases, news clippings, agendas, address, by-laws, pamphlets, notes. Includes Dewey C. Wayne, George O. Miller, James T. Duncan.
  - American Automobile Association, 1959, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    Statement, correspondence, analysis. Includes Russell E. Singer.
  - ACTION, Inc., 1959, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    Correspondence, pamphlet. Includes James E. Lash, American Council to Improve Our Neighborhoods.
  - American Institute of Cooperation, 1959, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 29 (a-f))
    Correspondence, memos, agendas, newsletters, remarks, pamphlets, remarks. Includes Jack L. Frost, C. F. McNamee, Calcot, Ltd., Sunsweet Growers, Inc.
  - American Trucking Associations, Inc., 1950-1961 (Box 15, Folder 30 (a-d))
    Addresss, bulletins, remarks, statements, correspondence, pamphlet. Includes John V. Lawrence.